♫ Snowing and blowing up bushels of fun. ♫
♫ Now the jingle hop has- ♫
♫ jingle bell, jingle bell jingle bell rock. ♫
♫ Jingle bells chime in jingle bell time. ♫
♫ Dancing and prancing in jingle bell square. ♫
♫ In the frosty air. ♫
♫ What a bright time it's the right time. ♫
♫ To rock the night away. ♫
♫ Jingle bell time is a swell time. ♫
♫ To go glidin' in a one-horse sleigh ♫
♫ Mix and a-mingle in the jinglin' feet. ♫
♫ That's the jingle bell rock ♫
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells jingle all the way. ♫
♫ Oh, what fun it is to ride in a one-horse open sleigh. ♫
♫ Dashing through the snow. ♫
♫ In a one-horse open sleigh. ♫
♫ O'er the hills we go. ♫
♫ Laughing all the way ♫
♫ It's the most wonderful time of the year ♫
♫ With the kids jingle-balling. ♫
♫ And everyone telling you "be of good cheer". ♫
♫ It's the most wonderful time of the year ♫
Leanne?
Oh, my God!
Listen carefully.
Your wife has been taken.
At 4:30 P.M.,
you will go to the Vatashca Street parking garage.
There, an level 2 you will find a very special car.
You will know which one.
Steal it.
There are cameras installed on the inside and outside of this vehicle.
I'm watching every move you make.
Drive it to the tap of the city and I will contact you there.
It's been a long time since you've driven...
But you'll have to overcome your fear if you want to save her.
Your wife is very beautiful.
If you want her back, then you will follow my instructions precisely.
If you contact the police, or if you get caught...
She will die.
You've done very well so far, Mr. magma.
During the course of this night,
you will be given several tasks.
If you fail at  any...
You will never see your wife again.
How do you like the car?
Do you like it?
It's armored.
It was designed especially for you.
Is she alive?
The police will be looking for you.
If they catch you,  ever...
The game's over. Is that clear?
Brent?
Why is this happening?
Please, help me. I'm so scared.
Where are you taking me? Where are you taking me? Wait!
She's fine.
For now.
She will remain that way as long as you follow my instructions.
I'm watching you, always.
Get rid of your phone.
What do you want?
Where are we?
No! Please, please, don't leave me here!
No!
Answer.
Speed up.
Faster.
Turn left.
Go through the intersection and turn hard left.
No, I can't do that. I'll dead end into the park.
Just do it.
It's Christmas.
There's gotta be hundreds of people in there.
I won't ask again.
Shit.
Came an!
Get out of my way.
Drive toward the market.
Smash into everything you can.
I can't do this!
You have no choice.
Jesus.
Excellent. Now drive onto the skating rink.
There's tan many people!
Now.
Get out of the way!
Go straight to the stage where the man is speaking. Knock it down.
-I'll kill him.     -Do it.
-Are you crazy?     -Now.
Now go down the stairs.
Ah, shit.
Ah...
Mr. magma, are you there?
Confirm you're still receiving.
I can hear you.
Where's my wife?
Keep going. Now.
Watch out, watch out!
Oh, no, no!
Jesus.
Bravo, Mr. Magna. Your first task is complete.
Am I done?
We're just getting started, my boy.
We're just getting started.
Turn right, now.
-The water truck.     -Yeah?
Smash into it!
Don't stop.
Speed up.
-Faster.     -The light's red down there.
Go through it.
Jesus.
Wonderful, Mr. Brent magma.
Now turn right. Pull into the underground construction zone.
Relax...
And you will await further instructions.
Get out.
-Get out, now!     -All right.
Do not get out of the car.
You heard me asshole, get out.
Now.
-Look, you got the wrong car. Walk away...     -Now!
-I'm doing you a favor.     -Get out.
-You don't wanna... walk away.     -Get out.
-You don't wanna steal...     -Get out of the car!
-Drive away.     -I can't! I got a kid in the car!
-Get out! What'?     -Drive away now!
-Drive.     -What do you want meta do with her?
Drive away! Take her with you! Do it. Drive!
All right, all right, all right!
Get off of me, asshole!
Do not ever point a gun at me, you hear me'?
Do not ever point a gun at anyone!
Unh! Don't ever touch me like that again. Do you know what I could have done to you?
The hell are you doing?
Strap yourself in.
-I'm not doing shit!     -Put on your seatbelt.
-No!     -Strap yourself in.
-Where are you going?     -Dust strap yourself in!
Kill her.
She has seen you and she has seen the vehicle.
I'm not gonna do it. I can't do that.
You either shoot her...
Or I'm going to shoot your wife.
One.
Two.
What? What? No.
I can't do that!
I'm not a killer.
It's the right choice. You'll need her.
You can keep the car.
Can I get out new?
I'll let you off right up here.     -She is not to be set free.
-L... listen.     -She is not to be set free.
-Understood?     -It's understand.
Oh, great.
Oh, my God.
What did you do?
Pull aver!
Oh! Shit!
On, God.
-What the hell are you doing?     -Put on your seatbelt!
Shit.
Hey, hey! Do not touch that gun, all right?
-I need bath hands to drive this car!     -Let go of me, asshole!
Do not touch that gun!
I don't care. I hope we crash. Help me!
This guy's trying to kill me!
What are you doing?
Pull us over!
Get in! Get inside the car!
-This guy's crazy! Help me!     -Get inside this car, all right?
You understand me? Stay in the car!
Pull aver.
Please slaw dawn.
-Oh, we're gonna die.     -Shut up.
Oh, my God.
Shit.
No, no, no.
You're the shittiest driver I've ever seen.
Back off, back off. Jesus!
On, shit!
Is he dead?
I hope not.
Listen to me, all right.
I have gotta get this car out of the city right now,
or they're gonna murder my wife.
-You understand me'?     -Sure.
Let me give you a ward to the wise.
Next time you wanna steal a car, try to make sure that no one is in it.
-It works better.     -I'm not stealing it, you asshole. This is my car.
What'?
You probably don't understand this...
"Because you're a criminal."
Things in this world belong to people before people like you take them.
This car, which was really great...
Till you added all these cameras to drain the battery...
Belongs to me. How'd you find the car'?
I got a call from a cap saying he saw my car parked in the garage where I found you.
What makes you think it was a cap?
Because he said so, genius.
What kind of cap calls to tell you he's got your car...
But he still leaves me inside of it?
-It wasn't the police that called.     -Then who was it?
I don't know.
-When was it stolen?     -Whenever you stale it.
When was the last time you saw it?
Two days ago, I guess. Look, you're obviously very disturbed.
Whatever trouble you're in, you deserve it.
Sc I'll cut you a deal. Pull aver and I'll let you walk away.
Or what, you shunt me?
Give me back my gun and I will.
What's a kid doing with a gun, huh?
Sc if some dipshit like you steps to me, I can take care of it.
That worked out well for you, didn't it?
Did you recognize the voice, huh, that voice?
-Your friend who wanted you to kill me'?     -He's not my friend, okay'?
I'm not the kind of person you wanna be caught kidnapping.
Yeah?
You special, is that it?
Just do me one favor, will you?
Shut the hell up.
You shut up!
What are you doing? Hey.
What the hell?
I can't believe you threw my phone out the window.
-I have a lot of money, you know.     -Good for you.
As in, if you let me go, I can give you a lot of money.
I don't want your money.
What do you want?
I want you to stop talking.
And I want my wife back.
-And he tank her?     -He did.
Whatever you awe him, I can get however much it is to pay him off, no problem.
We'll take care of it right now.
You have to let me go and stop almost killing us.
I would love to let you out of this car. Unfortunately, I can't do that.
Why the hell not?
Because he asked me not to and I am doing whatever he asks.
Se, what? What are you supposed to do?
I don't know.
Well, who is he?
-I don't know.     -What do you know?
Not much.
No, no, no!
Get up!
-Shut up.     -Ow! Aah!
Please. Please. Please, don't shunt me. Please, don't shunt me.
Quiet.
Answer.
It's time for your next task.
What is it?
More police are coming.
You'll have four minutes to getaway.
You'll follow my instructions exactly.
Someone wants to say hello.
Please, please.
Leanne?
Please. Help.
The clock starts now.
Damn it!
I'm totally screwed.
Oh!
-Ram him.     -What are you doing?
-Oh, my God.     -Keep going.
You're an idiot. That's assault with a deadly weapon.
They could shunt at us now.
-Speed up.     -Shit.
Turn right now.
Remember,
if they catch you...
You'll be a widower.
-Turn left.     -Oh, shit.
-Force him off the road.     -Look out!
-This is not very subtle!     -What are you talking about?
You're not making yourself very hard to find.
God, I promise I'll be good from new an. Please let me live.
-You're really not helping, okay'?     -Turn right.
Great.
Turn right down the alley.
Skip!
Holy shit.
-Two minutes.     -We're gonna die, please stop!
I don't think you'll make it.
What are you doing?
Take a deep breath, okay? And calm down.
Shit.
I wouldn't relax just yet.
-Shit.     -Not again.
-Did you think we were done?     -No, don't!
Goa!
You're running out of time.
Oh! Oh!
Tick tock, tick tock.
You have less than a minute.
-Turn into the park.     -No, not the park!
Here we go.
Your wife's time is running out.
Watch out! Unh!
Go through the intersection.
All right, hold an!
Not much time, Mr. magma.
Oh, no!
-No, please don't! Don't!     -Yep, yep, yep, hold on!
Five...
Four... Came an, came an, came an!
Three...
-...mo...     -Oh!
One...
Zero.
Bravo, Mr. Magna. Well done.
Bravo.
Your wife lives...
For now.
Well dune.
Answer.
"Brent Magna is both reckless and fearful."
"He is, in short..."
"...a dangerous driver and should pursue another profession."
Remember that review? It wasn't very flattering.
They're blind to your real talents...
Which are perfectly suited to my needs.
Do I know you?
I know you, Mr. magma...
-and I believe in you.     -Listen.
I need to know when this is all gonna be aver, all right? I need...
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
-I hate you.     -Yeah, I love you.
You realize I'll just have to buy another limited edition shelby super snake...
Take another six months to re-time the earns, open up the intake and customize it.
And then I'm gonna drive it aver your face.
-You sure know a lot about cars for...     -A girl'?
Yeah.
Wow.
I like fast cars and computers and bay things, haw butch.
It's the 21st century, you should join it.
-What are you doing?     -I'm documenting this shit.
I'm not going to jail after we get arrested.
-Well, nobody's gonna get caught, okay'?     -That's right, I forgot.
We're just gonna die...
"Because you're a dumb-ass who attacks the police with a damn car."
New every cap in this entire country...
Is hoping to put a couple bullets in our heads. Goad plan.
-We are alive.     -Barely.
Not much of a thinker are you?
Well, I didn't actually graduate from charm school like you...
So maybe someday you can give me some tutoring or something.
This is what he did to my beautiful, beautiful paint jab.
Just get in the car.
This is all the crap that he drilled into my carbon fiber interior.
This is the dumb-ass who got me into this mess.
-Stop filming me, all right'?     -Wave hi to the judge.
-Say hi to all your new friends in jail.     -Hey! Put that away! I'm trying... just stop it.
What is...? You're like add or something. What are you fiddling with new?
-Stop doing that.     -Why'?
Because this guy is watching us, okay?
-I need you to stop...     -I know what I'm doing.
-Dust listen to me for two seconds.      -I know what I'm doing.
See, I went to school and I know things...
Which is why I don't have to steal stuff, like some people.
If you're so smart, you tell me what's going on with all these cameras, huh?
They're all linked to a single feed.
It's not only encrypted, but it's piggybacking on a public server.
Huh?
It means they're hosting this live feed from these cameras...
An a government server without them knowing about it.
Sc anybody can watch it, even us.
-Wait a second.     -What?
-These aren't coming from the same place.     -Where are they coming from?
Lacks like a parking garage.
-Can you tell where it is?     -I don't know. Could be anywhere.
-Do you think it's where he might be'?     -Doubt it. But he can see it.
I don't like that he's watching us.
Do you think you can track him with that thing?
No, and if anyone did, he would just dump the ip address.
As long as his feed is hosted remotely, there's no way to find it.
-And that thing isn't really well-hidden.     -What?
Microphone.
-Oh, so he's listening to us too'?     -Probably.
Well, I'll give you this, you are bright.
It's called being educated.
You should look into it when you're not committing crimes.
Scratch that, you'll be in jail.
All right, answer.
Pull up power plant on the GPS.
We're kind of busy right now.
Learn to multitask.
Or let your new little friend help you. Lack under the visor.
Won't you do that?
I'm uploading a new set of directions.
That's the city power plant.
"At exactly 11:30."
You will be there.
Why are we going to the power plant?
Always so inquisitive.
I like it.
Listen carefully,
you're to break into the central roam.
Access the remote system...
-and insert that drive.     -What will that do?
You're a clever girl. I'm sure you'll figure it out.
He wants to cut the power off. Why do you want to cut the power?
You have some time until 11:30.
I wouldn't spend it trying to figure out my motives.
He's a real asshole.
So you don't know who that is?
No.
-No idea?     -I gut ideas.
People I used to work with...
But nobody I know could set up something like this.
So why you'?
Because I can drive.
-That's debatable.     -No, I mean, I used to race.
Really?
Really.
Professionally, like, real racing.
Don't think I ever saw you an TV.
There was a couple weeks there where you might have.
And?
And what?
I washed out.
How come'?
I don't know, I just did. Doesn't matter now.
That's a pretty shitty answer.
I washed out because I believed everybody who told me haw great I was.
Turns out the only thing I was great at was wrecking expensive cars.
Sc I fell off the pro circuit and I awed a bunch of money.
This is the only thing I was ever any good at...
So I took whatever job paid the most.
I did some things I'm not proud of.
But then I got out of it. And this...
Is why.
She's beautiful.
-Is she from here?     -Yeah.
She always wanted to came back, so we thought...
It'd be a good place to lay law and start aver.
Then I came home from work today, the dour is busted open...
The place is a wreck, there's bland on the floor.
My cell phone rings and this voice tells me...
if I ever wanna s...
If I ever wanna see her again...
I gotta do this jab.
And if I tell anyone, she'll be dead.
Next thing I know, I'm driving around in your car.
You souped this thing up yourself?
Yeah, it was a graduation present.
Nice. Something tells me your dad's not a mechanic.
He's the ceo of one of the largest banks in town.
We moved here about two years ago for him to take it over.
I barely see him,
but this car is the nicest gift he ever gave me.
Well, I'm sorry about all the damage.
You know, you could also apologize for taking me hostage.
You could apologize for putting a gun in my face.
I will if you let me out.
There's only one thing I'm concerned about right now...
And I'm gonna do whatever I have to to get her back.
Sc if he says you gotta stay in the car, you gotta stay in the car.
And where does that get you?
Why is this happening? What is he after?
You clearly haven't thought this through.
What happens when this is done and he gets what he wants?
Why would he even give her back to you?
If I were him, I'd kill her and I'd probably kill you.
Shit.
What?
I'd probably kill me tan.
Lacks like they've already been here.
If he was already here, why didn't he just take out the power himself?
I don't know.
Stop here.
Why?
Ever see what happens to a metal car...
When it touches a transformer that powers the whale city?
Dust wait here, I'll handle it.
What, alone?
Yeah, just be ready to go.
You sure?
Turn the car around, that's what I should do.
No, I should gain after her.
No, she's fine. She knows what she's doing.
Hello? I don't have much time.
I'm in this car with this man and his wife was kidnapped.
I speak English. Calm yourself.
Could you just send someone, please?
-What is your, uh, emergency?     -I don't know.
It's this voice telling us what to do. You have to help us.
-Exactly what is your location?     -I'm at the power plant.
-You make it so much fun.     -Shit.
Wherever that clever mind takes you, remember, I've already been there.
Look around.
You see? That's right.
The police will think you blew up the power station.
Can I give you some advice?
Run.
Come on, come on.
-Go, go, go!     -What, what, what?
-Drive, drive! Go!     -What happened?
Hold on. Shit.
Aah!
Faster!
Go faster!
Oh!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
I'm not dying for you.
-What happened?     -This is a part of his plan.
I was an camera that whale time.
He could have taken out the power himself, but he lured us in there...
"Because he wanted me to get caught an camera doing it."
You think the caps would ever believe me new?
Before, it was just you...
This car.
But new I'm screwed tan.
I'm sorry.
I gotta take care of myself.
Answer.
Stop her from leaving.
Go to hell.
Where are you taking me? Where are you taking me? Wait. Wait.
Leanne'? Leanne, can you hear me'?
Can you-f? Please.
Leanne, can you hear me?
Brent. Brent, what's going on?
Are you okay? Have they hurt you?
-Why is this happening?     -Leanne.
-Please help me! Brent?     -Leanne, are you all right, baby?
Please help me! I'm so scared.
I'm coming after you. I'm gonna make all this better.
-I'm gonna get...     -Aah!
What...?
Put my wife back an! Put her back an!
Is my wife all right?
I told you not to let her out of the car.
-I just need to see if she's...     -I warned you.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
I know what it's like to disappoint everyone, but I never thought that I'd let her dawn.
She's still alive.
You don't have to do this.
I want to.
What are you doing?
We gotta figure out his plan.
On, shit.
Get dawn, get dawn. Came an.
Okay, okay.
He was having you make this.
You're blocking off a path.
Half of these are one-way streets.
With these intersections blacked off, no one will be able to get through here.
Until they clean this mess up, there'll only be one way out of the city.
The rest will be a total shit show.
It's an escape route.
I just wish I knew what he was after.
You and me bath.
-Answer.     -I have good news for you.
This is your last assignment.
Look up number five in the GPS.
Follow the directions precisely. You have 10 minutes.
It's the bank.
What bank?
He wants us to rub my dad's bank.
Oh, shit.
We can't do that.
Do as instructed. The clock is ticking.
You can't. There's no way we could do that. The security's way tan tight.
Don't concern yourself with security.
-He wants us to get caught.     -Follow the GPS. Turn around.
This is a suicide mission. Listen, we can't do this.
Ignore her. Listen to me. Turn around now.
Am I gonna see my wife again?
Turn around.
I'm losing my patience with you.
Listen to me.
No.
I need to know when I'm going to see my wife.
No, turn the car around.
This is your last warning.
I need to be told that she is all right
and when this shit is gonna be aver!
Do you want to see her again?
Get control of yourself and turn the car around.
You can't do this.
-Listen to me, this is a setup.     -He will kill her.
That's why they used my car. It had to be me.
Think about it.
My dad, he cut off all of my funds.
New my car is causing havoc all aver the city...
And I'm seen rubbing his bank?
He wants us to get caught.
-What does he wanna steal?     -Money.
But that's just it, it's not that kind of bank.
What do you mean?
My dad runs an investment bank.
-There's no cash.     -Oh, shit!
-God.     -So, what, safety deposit boxes?
No, there's nothing like that in there, just computers.
-Bands. Bearer bands.     -Bearer bands? How old are you?
What is he after, then?
What's he trying to steal?
Unless...
Hold an!
Unless what?
Unless you don't want a record of your money.
-Right, right, like it's dirty money.     -Exactly.
-How do you move dirty money?     -Look out, look out!
-Came an, help me.     -They could encrypt the information...
An a numeric transfer key. A flash drive with account numbers.
If you stale one of these little transfer keys, right...?
-You could drain the accounts.     -Right.
No one would report that money stolen, it's not supposed to exist.
-Haw much are we talking about?     -It could be billions.
I should have been a banker.
Tell me that you're not serious.
Shit!
-I'm gonna go for it.     -No, don't go for it!
Here we go!
That was awesome.
Aah!
Aah! Get us out of here!
Watch out.
I really, really hate you.
I can understand that.
-What are you doing?     -Dust wait.
Okay, just sit still and be quiet for a minute.
Okay, it's dune. I bought us some time.
What?
I hacked into the server connected to these cameras, put an a loop of us driving.
-That's what he can see right now.     -Why?
Sc that you'll listen to me.
When we get there, we're gonna get caught and your wife will die.
We're his decays.
-Great.     -The powers out...
Which means the security infrastructure has been compromised.
And when that happens, there's a procedure.
Oh, shit.
My dad said something about this.
They're being moved. They're moving them right now.
They move anything sensitive to a secure location until the system is back up...
...and then they run a million tests.
By the time we get there...
We'll be rubbing an empty bank.
Please, let's just find a place to lack at it first.
I guarantee you it's swarming with caps.
How long do we have?
I don't know, five, maybe 10 minutes at the mast.
Watch where you're going, asshole!
I'll go check it.
Sc you were right?
I wish I wasn't.
Se, what do we do new?
I'm thinking.
You said there was a procedure. If the power goes out,
they'll move the drives?
Yeah.
Where do they move them?
I don't know, it's classified information for the bank.
Right. Shit.
But they gotta get picked up. They have to be picked up from here.
They've got all these caps here waiting for us.
I mean, what, is there a back door? Is there another entrance?
Remember that parking spat that we saw?
You asked if I thought that's where he was?
Yeah.
Well, I bet he's there now.
I told you you were bright.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Three, one,
nine, seven, two,
one, three, four,
two, six.
What?
Go, go, go!
-You got it'?     -Yeah, go!
Get them!
Answer me.
Answer me, answer me.
Answer!
Answer.
You're dead. Your wife is dead. It's over! Don't play with me!
We hold the cards new, asshole!
Could you be a little bit more careful?
How do I get this drive out?
Gut it!
Knack him! Hit him!
The voice speaks in german
Holy shit!
Oh. My God, go!
-Get down, get down, get down!     -Do something!
Please, get us out of here!
Oh!
Look out!
Hold on!
his is Sofia police department.
Shit!
Pull aver the car now!
Lose them.
Driver, pull aver car now!
We're trapped. Sit back. Hold an. You ready?
All right. Where's the gun? Where's the gun?
-Give me the gun!     -Keep your hands where we can see them.
New, just go with me on this, all right? Just go with me.
Back off!
Or I will shunt her head! I will blow her brains out!
Back off! Hey! Hey! See this?
Back off, or I'm killing this girl, you hear me?
I will kill this girl right now
What the hell are you doing?
I am going to blow her head off! Now, you. You. Yeah, you!
You okay? Hey!
Back, back, back! Or I'm killing this girl, you hear me?
Back off! Back off!
That's it, you're doing great.
Get out of my way, copper.
I can't believe that worked.
They're clear. I've sent you their location.
Intercept them.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna let you out.
What?
Came an. You're not a suspect anymore.
They think I kidnapped you. Tell them you were a hostage.
-No, I'm...     -I'm serious. I'm serious.
You've done more than enough for me.
I can't risk your life anymore.
-I really can't. You gotta get out, okay?     -No.
-Get out of the car.     -No.
Came an, get out of the car, will you?
I'm coming with you.
You're an extremely stubborn person, all right, you know that?
I know.
But I'm still not getting out of this car.
Besides, without me, you'd probably do something stupid, like get your face shat off.
All right.
You don't even know my name, do you?
No.
Aah! Go!
Damn it!
-Ow!     -Are you all right?
Hit him!
Damn it!
Get dawn, get dawn!
Dawn!
Lack out!
Oh, God.
Get us off the train!
-Where's the gun? Find the gun!     -I don't know!
-Find the gun!     -I'm lacking!
Find it!
-You got it'? Give it to me!     -I found it! Here!
Just hold the wheel for a second!
I need you to downshift! You ready?
Now!
I have an idea.
Get out.
Sc we meet up with him.
We do an exchange. The drive for your wife.
It'll never work. He'll kill us.
I have a way around it.
We use his camera to feed the video to the caps.
They'll see everything.
Answer the phone.
-Answer.     -You think you are so smart?
-I wouldn't be so...    -no, shut up and listen.
We have what you want, let's make a trade.
Where?
You know where I work?
I'll see you there in two hours.
Goodnight, asshole.
Where's my wife?
Where's my drive?
No. No! No!
Leanne!
Brent?
I need to know they're real.
You.
Fallow him.
Let her go first.
Oh, thank God you're here.
I love you.
I'm waiting.
Waiting.
Let's go.
Shoot them.
Brent, look out!
No! No!
-Throw her in!      -No! Aah!
-Are you all right?     -I'm okay.
Shit, they gut the kid.
-I gotta go after her.     -Go get her.
You stay with the police. Be careful.
Damn it!
Are you hurt, ma'am?
Shit.
He has a gun an me.
Brent, he has a gun.
Please hear me.
-I hope you can see this.     -sh
Quiet! Don't talk.
Brent, I'm trying to show you where we are.
Move out of my way!
Brent, yes!
-You're screwed, asshole!     -Shut up!
Come on, come on.
Oh!
Damn it!
What are you doing? Is that a camera?
Give it to me, give it to me! No, give it back!
Ah, shit! Bastard.
Damn it!
On, shit.
Shit.
The only way out of the city.
I know where she is.
-Pull aver! Give me the gun!     -What are you doing? Stop it!
You want us to die?
Brent'. Came an, came an!
-Get out!     -What?
Now!
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Yeah.
Stay there. You're under arrest.
Thanks.
Everybody back!
Ugh!
-I guess I owe you one, huh?     -And you owe me a new car.
Don't worry about the car. It just needs a new paint jab and she'll be fine.
-What's that?     -I don't know.
It's not mine.
-Hello'?     -Aren't you going to thank me?
I did for you what you could never do for yourself.
I showed you what you are made of.
Please  excuse me if I wasn't able to be there in person.
I'm sure you understand, under the circumstances...
It would have been most inconvenient for me.
If you're asking yourself who I am to you...
I am your greatest fan.
I always thought you could have been at the top of your profession...
If only you believed you could.
So that's it, you see.
Please send your lovely wife my best wishes for a happy Christmas.
I'm sincerely glad you worked things out to be with her for the holidays.
It's the season to be together with loved ones, so pm told.
I have very few loved ones.
My consolation is I have a lot of money.
And now, quite a lot more of it, thanks to you.
I doubt if our paths will cross again, but then, life is full of surprises.
So let's just say au
revoir.
Be assured,
it's been most entertaining.
死路十条
索非亚 保加利亚
道路封闭
警察局
来电
呼叫
加载外部设备
加载进度
死路十条
琳恩？
喔，天啊！
仔细听好了
你的妻子在我们手上
下午四点半
到Vitasha停车场二楼
你会看到一辆很特别的车
你知道我什么意思
抢过来
车里有录影镜头
我能看到你的一举一动
开车到山顶，我会再跟你联系
我知道因为那次意外你很久没有开车了…
但你必须克服你的恐惧，如果你还想救你的妻子
你的妻子很漂亮
如果你想她回到你身边，那就按照我的指令行动
如果你打算报警，或者你被逮捕…
你就再也看不到她了
到目前为止你做的很好，麦格纳先生
今晚的过程中
您将获得各项任务
如果你失败了…
你永远不会再看到你的妻子
那辆车怎么样？
喜欢吗？
改进了装甲
是特别为你设计的
我妻子还活着吗？
警察会一直追捕你
如果你被逮捕…
游戏就结束，明白吗？
布兰特？
发生了什么事？
求求你，救我，我怕极了
要去哪里？要去哪里？等等！
她没事
至少现在没事
只要你老老实实按我说的做
我会一直看着你的
把手机扔掉
你想要做什么？
要带我去哪里？
不！求求你，放我出去！
不要！
我在
加速
再加速
左转
穿过十字路口一直往前
不行，前面是个公园
按我说的做
今天是圣诞节
公园里有很多人
我不是在征求你的意见
妈的
闪开！
快闪开
去市场
你完全可以撞死他们
我不能！
你别无选择的
天啊！
很好，现在去溜冰场
哇靠！那里人更多！
快去
都给我闪开！
到舞台那里，撞死那个演讲的
-撞死他  -快去
-你就是个神经病？  -快去
现在冲下楼梯
喔，我靠
喔…
麦格纳先生，还在吗？
快回答
我还没死
我的妻子在哪？
我们继续  快！
小心，小心！
不，不，不！
天啊
布兰特·麦格纳先生，你的第一个任务完成了
是么？
我们才刚开始
来我们继续
右转
-前面有辆饮料车  -喔？
撞过去！
别停
加速
-快！  -前面是红灯！
闯过去
天啊
太漂亮了，布兰特·麦格纳先生
现在右转，去地下停车场
放轻松…
等待下一步指示
滚出去
-滚出去，快！  -好了
别下车
没听到吗？滚出去！快！
快！
-你上错了车…  -快！
-我有一个建议  -快滚出去
-滚出去！  -快！
-你最好别抢这辆车…  -快滚出去！
-快开车  -靠！你没看到这有个女孩吗！
-滚出去！  -快开车！
-开车  -现在怎么办？！
把她带上！快开车！快点！
好了，好了，好了！
把你的手拿开，你个混蛋！
不要再拿枪指着我！
也不要指着任何人！
你也不要再碰我！
什么情况？你他妈在干什么？
系好安全带
-我才不系！  -系好安全带
-就不系！  -系好安全带
-你要去哪里？  -系好安全带！
杀了她
她见过你，见过这辆车
不行，我做不到
杀了她…
或者我杀了你妻子
1…
2…
什么？什么？不
我不能杀了她！
我不是杀人犯！
明智的选择，你还用得到她
你继续在车里呆着
我能下车吗？
-为什么？你害怕了吗？  -她不能走
-听…我说！  -她不能下车，明白吗？
-明白了吗？  -明白
非常好
天啊
你干什么？
靠边！
我靠！
天啊
-你到底干了什么？  -系好安全带！
我靠
嘿！嘿！别碰枪？好吗？
-我要两只手才能开车！  -放开我，混蛋！
不要再碰那把枪！
我才不管，你最好撞坏这辆车
救命！这个大叔要杀我！
你在犯什么神经？
快让车停下来！救命！
快回来！
-他想杀我！救命！  -快回来！好吗？
给我老老实实呆在车里！
靠边
快减速
-我靠，我会死的  -闭嘴
天啊
我靠！
靠，靠，靠
你是我见过的最烂的车手
闪开，快闪开！
我靠！
他死了吗？
我希望没有
听我说，行吗？
我现在必须要开车出城
不然他们会杀了我妻子
-你明白了吗？  -当然
听我一句劝，你下次偷车的时候
先看看里面有没有人
-就不会碰到这样的事了  -我不是偷车贼，这辆车是我的，傻逼
什么？
你不知道，因为…
你才是偷车贼
这世上每个东西都有自己的主人，但总有人喜欢偷走它
这辆装着镜头、电池、天线…
的车是我的…
那你是怎么找到这车的？
警察打电话给我，说看到我的车停在一个车库里，于是我就找到了你
你怎么知道他就是警察？
当然是他说的啊，天才
哪个警察会告诉你的车在哪…
却不带你一起去？
-他根本不是警察  -那他是谁？
我不知道
-车是什么时候被偷了？  -你偷的你问我？
最后一次看到这车是什么时候？
我记得应该是两天前，你看起来很不对劲
无论你碰到任何麻烦都是你自己的事情，现在我们来作笔交易
靠边，乖乖滚下车，我就不会报警抓你
不然呢？你要打死我？
把枪给我，我很愿意效劳
什么样的小孩会像你这样用枪？
所以如果再碰到你这样的白痴，我会小心的
这对你来说很好，不是吗？
你听不听得出这是谁的声音？
-你的朋友要你杀了我？  -这不是我朋友
我不是你以为的容易被绑架的人
喔？是么？
你跟普通人不一样，对吗？
帮我一个忙可以吗？
闭上你的嘴
你才给我闭嘴！
你在做什么？
你在犯什么神经？
真不敢相信你把我的手机扔了出去
-我有很多钱，你知道吗？  -看得出来
如果你放我走，我可以给你很多钱
我不要钱
那你想要什么？
我要你闭嘴
我要救我老婆
-他绑架了你妻子？  -对
好吧，我不管你们谁欠谁的
这都不管我的事情
我不想在这死的不明不白
我也想放你出去，但是不行
为什么？
因为他要我带着你，因为我必须按他说的做
那你打算怎么办？
我不知道
他是谁？
-我不知道  -那你知道些什么？
不多
不，不，不！
起床！
-闭嘴  -哇！啊！
求求你，别这样，求求你
闭嘴
我在
你的下一个任务的时间
是什么呢？
警察追来了
你有4分钟的时间逃脱
严格按照我的指示
有人想跟你打个招呼
求求你，求求你
琳恩？
求求你，救救我
现在开始计时
我靠！
完蛋了
喔！
-加速前冲  -你要干什么？
-天啊  -继续开
你这个白痴，他们
会杀了你的
-加速  -靠
右转，就是现在
不要忘了
如果你被逮捕…
你的妻子就不保了
-左转  -我靠
-把他撞开  -小心！
-我简直不能相信是真的！  -你在说什么？
你以后最好不要让我看到你
上帝，我今后一定好好做人，快救救我吧
-你确定不能闭上嘴吗？  -右转
非常好
右转进巷子！
住手！
我靠！
-2分钟  -我们会死的，快停下来！
我不认为你能成功
你在做什么？
深呼吸，放松点
我靠
如果我是你，我就没这么乐观
-靠  -不要
-你逃脱了吗？  -不，不要！
天啊！
你的时间不多了
喔！喔！
滴答，滴答
不到一分钟了
-进入公园  -别进去！
没事的，我们进去
时间已经快到了
小心！
冲过路口
再坚持一下！
没有时间了，麦格纳先生
天啊！
-不！别这样！  -坚持就快了！
5…
4…快，快，快啊！
3…
-2…  -喔！
1…
0！
布兰特·麦格纳先生，干得好！
完美
你的妻子还活着…
现在
干得好
我在
‘布伦特·麦格纳是一个鲁莽可怕的人’
‘是一个，嗯…’
‘一个危险的车手，应该尽早换一份工作’
你还记得他吗？惹人厌的家伙
他们无视你真正的才华
但我非常看好你
我认识你吗？
我认识你，麦格纳先生…
-而且我愿意相信你  -听我说
你什么时候才能放我老婆出来？我要…
你在做什么？
嘿，你打算干什么？
-我恨你  -是么，我爱你
你知道吗我要重新买一辆谢尔比超级蛇限量版…
再花六个月的时间来改装
然后我要开着它压过你的脸
-你很懂机械，虽然你是个…  -是个女孩？
对
哇喔
我喜欢跑车、电脑、很Man的东西
现在是21世纪了，你应该考虑加入我们
-你在做什么？  -我要录证据
被捕后我才不要去坐牢
-没有人会被捕，好吗？  -喔对，我差点忘了
我们会直接挂掉…
就因为你这个白痴，攻击警察
现在全国每一个警察都想抓到我们…
在我们的头上来两枪
-我们还活着  -勉强活着
你又不是个伟大的思想家？
你知道吗，其实我还没有毕业…
所以你或许还能教我点什么
看看他干的好事，我帅气的跑车
快回来坐好
看看我的碳纤维车盖
这就是那个白痴，让我陷入了这个烂摊子
-别录了  -跟法官打个招呼吧
-向你的狱友问个好  -快关掉
你现在又在干什么？
-老实点可以吗？  -为什么要听你的？
因为这家伙在看着我们
-我希望你能安静一会…  -我知道我在干什么
-你能安静的呆2秒听我说吗？  -我知道我在干什么
我在学校接受到过教育…
这就是为什么我不必去偷东西，不像某些人
既然你这么聪明，能不能告诉我这些相机是怎么回事
所有相机都连接到同一个端口
没有加密，但是盗用了政府伺服器
喔？
也就是说
他们能直接使用政府伺服器
可以看到城市里所有角落
-等等  -怎么了？
-这些端口不来自同一个地方  -来自于哪里？
看起来是个地下停车场
-你能获取具体位置吗？  -没办法，它可能在任何一个地方
-你觉得会在哪里？  -我不确定
但他可以看到我们，让我很不爽
您可以追踪到他吗？
不行，如果有人试图追踪，他就会改变IP地址
只要他用的是伺服器，就有没有办法找到它
-但是有其他方法  -什么？
麦克风
-你还在听这个？  -或许吧
好我不得不承认，你很聪明
这就是所谓的礼貌
你应该尝试停止继续犯罪
如果你继续这样，他们会把你送进监狱
我在
看导航仪上的地图
我现在有点忙
你要学会一心两用
或者向你的小伙伴寻求帮助
你能把遮阳板放下来吗？
我发送了一个新的路线图
发电厂
晚上十一点半
我在那等你
为什么我们要去发电厂？
既然你诚心诚意的发问了，我就告诉你
因为我喜欢
现在听我说
我要你到控制室里
进入远程伺服器…
-把这个密匙插进去  -你要干什么？
你是个聪明的女孩，你一定明白的
他要切断电源，你为什么要切断电源？
还要过一会才到十一点半
如果我是你，我不会浪费时间来了解我的动机
他是一个彻底的混蛋
你不知道他是谁
对
-也没有任何头绪？  -我有一些猜测
可能是以前和我一起工作的人…
但我知道没有人会安排这些事情
为什么他选择你？
因为我是个优秀的车手
-关于这点还有待商确  -我的意思是在赛车场上
真的假的？
真的
专业，真正的赛车
我不记得我在电视上见过你
是啊，你在那可能有几个星期了
什么？
什么什么？
我退出了比赛
怎么个情况？
我也不知道，反正就是退出了，现在说这个没意义
真是个完美的回答
我退出因为有人夸我有多么伟大
原来我唯一擅长的就是撞毁昂贵的赛车
我不再比赛后，欠了很多钱
赛车是我唯一擅长的事情…
对此我倾注了很多心血
我赢了很多比赛，但我并不感到光荣
然后我就走了，而这个…
我的妻子
她很漂亮
-她是我们这儿的人？  -对
她一直想回来，我们认为这会是个好地方…
慢慢重新开始生活
我今天下班回家，看到大门开着…
地板上有血迹
然后我接到电话，告诉我说…
如果我想…
如果我想再次见到我的妻子…
我就必须按他们说的做
如果我告诉任何人这事，我妻子就死定了
然后我就开着你的车
你改装了这辆车？
对，这是我的毕业礼物
调试的很好，也看出你父亲不是一个机械师
他是我们这里最大银行的CEO
我们大约两年前搬到这里
之后就很少看到他
但这辆车是他给我的最好的礼物
很抱歉把你车搞成这样
你道歉我也不一定就要原谅你
你也可以一枪打爆我的头
如果你让我出去的话我会的
现在我只关心一件事…
我会不惜一切代价救我的妻子
所以他说要你留在车上，你就得呆着
为什么你就得听他的
为什么发生这些事？他到底要干什么？
你显然没有想过这些问题
当这一切结束时会发生什么事？
为什么他会让你妻子回来？
如果我是他，我会杀了你妻子
我靠
怎么了？
可能也会杀了我
看起来他们已经来过这里
如果他在这里，为什么不自己去切断电源？
我不知道
停车
怎么了？
你不知道吗，金属的车辆…
靠近变压器会被电流击穿的
在这等着，我来处理
等等，什么？
我要进去
你确定吗？
我应该把车开出去
不对，我应该开进去
不对，她很清醒，她知道她在做什么
哈罗？听得到吗？我时间紧迫
我与一名男子在车上，他的妻子被绑架
请慢慢说英语
快点派人来，快点！
-情况有多紧急？  -我不知道
有人打电话命令我们按他说的做，你必须帮帮我们
-位置是在哪里呢？  -我在发电厂
-哈哈哈，你很机灵  -妈的
不管在哪里都很聪明，我已经去过那里了
看看你的周围
看到了吗？就是那个
警察会认为是你炸毁电厂的
过度充电
我有个建议给你
快跑
快，快啊
-走，走，快走！  -发生什么事了？
-救命，救命啊！快走！  -发生什么事了？
坚持一下，妈的
啊！
加速！
快加速！
喔！
你在做什么？你在做什么？
我不想因为你去坐牢！
-发生了什么事？  -这是他的计划的一部分
我刚才被监控拍下了
他玩弄我们在鼓掌之中…
他在一步步诱导我们
你以为警察现在还会相信我们吗？
开始这只是你自己的事情…
还把我的车拖下水
现在，我也被牵扯进来了
对不起
我会照顾好我自己
我在
不能让她走
见鬼去吧
要去哪里？要去哪里？等等！
琳恩！琳恩！你能听到吗？
听到吗？帮帮忙
琳恩，你能听到我吗？
布兰特，这是怎么回事？
你还好吗？他们伤害你了吗？
-这是怎么回事？  -琳恩！
-救救我！布兰特  -琳恩！你受伤了，你还好吗？
快救救我！我好害怕
我马上就来救你，一切都会结束的，好吗？
-会结束的  -啊！
什么…？
放开我老婆！我要看到她！
你们把我老婆怎么样了？
我跟你说过不要让她下车
-我只是想看看…  -我警告过你
对不起
这不是你的错
我知道我很没用，但我不能放弃我老婆
她还活着
你没有义务帮我
我自愿的
你在做什么？
我猜到了他的计划
我靠
躲下去，快
什么都没有
他让你在路上制造混乱
警察封锁了很多路口
这些路口一半以上都是单行道
已经无法通行
现在只有一条路可以出城
其他的都走不通
这看起来是一个撤退路线
真想知道他到底要干什么
我也是
-我在  -有个好消息
这是你最后一个任务了
查看你的导航
按照这个路线开，你有十分钟
银行
哪家银行？
他想让我们抢我父亲的银行
我靠！
我们不会去的
计时已经开始了
我们两个人怎么可能抢的了银行
不要在意这些细节
-他就是想要我们被抓住  -注意看导航，掉头
这等于是自杀，我们不能去
别理她，听我指令，掉头
我要确定我妻子没事
快掉头
我耐心有限
我们好好商量可以吗？
没的商量
我什么时候才能看到我老婆
听我的指令
我最后一次警告你
我要看到她没事
什么时候才能结束这一切
你是不想再见到你妻子了吗？
把车开过去
你别听他的
-听我说！这是一个陷阱！  -他们会杀了我老婆
你知道为什么他们要用我的车吗？
仔细想想吧
我爸断了我的生活费
现在我的车在城里乱窜
然后所有人都看到我抢劫了银行？
他就是想让我当替罪羊
-他想要的是什么？  -当然是钱
这就是问题所在，它不是那种银行
什么意思？
我爸爸那是一家投资银行
-根本没有现金可以抢  -我靠！
-天啊  -你是什么意思，那只有保险柜？
也没有保险柜，那儿只有一堆电脑
-债券呢？不记名债券  -债券？现在什么年代了？
那他到底要干嘛？
他要偷的是什么？
除非…
坐稳！
除非什么？
除非你有一笔黑钱
-洗黑钱？  -没错
-怎么才能洗干净黑钱呢？  -小心，小心！
-快说说  -银行对账户数据进行加密的…
有一个数据传输密钥
如果能拿到这个密钥呢…？
-就可以使用那个账户  -对
没人会发现有钱被动过，账户根本就不存在
-会有多少钱？  -可能会有数十亿美元
我应该也去开个银行
你不会真的要
我靠！
-我会尽力的  -别，别这样
嘿喂狗！
我靠好险
啊！
啊！滚开！
小心！
我恨你一个洞
我晓得
-你在做什么？  -别废话！
好，我们保持冷静，安静的坐一会
打完收工，我们赢得了一点时间
什么意思？
我进入伺服器，把刚才录的一段视频循环播放
-这样他就暂时只能看到这个视频  -干嘛这样？
现在听我说
当我们到银行后，我们会被抓住，他会杀了你妻子
我们是他的诱饵
-非常好  -现在切断了电源…
银行的安全系统就失效了
当发生这种情况，会启动一个应急机制
我靠
我父亲曾经提到过这个的
转移，现在正在转移
把重要的数据转移到一个安全的地方…
…直到系统恢复正常
等我们到达银行的时候…
只有一个空荡荡的银行
现在我们要找个地方静观其变
我保证银行周围全都是警察
我们有多少时间？
五到十分钟
看你能去哪里，混蛋！
我去看看
怎么样了？
很糟糕
现在该怎么办？
我正在想
你之前说如果电力中断他们就会
转移数据？
对
转去哪里？
我不知道，这是银行的机密
我靠
但是他们要过去拿对不对，他们已经快得手了
而所有警察都在这里
这儿有后门或其他入口吗？
记得那个停车场吗？
你觉得他会在那里吗？
有可能
我敢打赌，他就在那里
你可能是对的
我们走
接入码
3，1…
9，7，2…
1，3，4…
2，6…
什么？
快，快，快！
-好了  -走吧！
快追上去！
接电话
接电话，接电话
给我接电话！
我在
你死定了，你老婆完了，游戏结束！
现在我们占上风，混蛋！
你可以开稳一点吗？
等我拔出密钥？
到手了！
撞他！撞他！
你妹的！
我靠！
天啊，快走！
趴下！趴下！
快离开这鬼地方
喔！
小心！
坐稳！
索非亚警方
我靠
靠边停车！
放弃抵抗
车里的人，立刻靠边停车
我们被困住了，准备好了了吗？
枪？枪呢？
-把枪给我！  -你已经被包围了
好了跟我来，走
别过来！
不然我打爆她的头！
退后！没看到吗？
退后，我会杀了她的
我会杀了她的
我要打爆她的头！
嘿！你！你！对就是你！
你还好吗？
都退后，我会杀了她的？
退后！
对很好，就这样
快闪开，条子们
真不敢相信这是我干的
他们还没被捕，我把位置给你
抓住他们
怎么了？
你快离开这
什么？
你不再有嫌疑
他们会认为你是被我绑架的
-不，我…  -我说真的
你已经尽力了
我不能再让你冒生命危险
-你必须离开这  -不行
-下车  -不
走吧，你快走吧
我要跟你一起去
你真是个固执的人？
我知道
我不会离开我的车
如果我不在你要打算怎么办
好吧
你还不知道我叫什么名字吧？
不知道
喔！快走！
我靠！
-哇！  -你没事吧？
撞他！
趴下！
趴好！
小心！
天啊
要掉下去了！
-枪在哪里？  -我不知道！
-枪在哪里？  -我在找！
快找枪！
-找到了吗？快给我  -在这在这儿呢
帮我扶一下方向盘！
帮我挂到低档，准备好了吗？
快！
我有一个想法
下车
我们去找他
我们用数据换你的妻子
他不会答应的，他会把我们都杀了
我有一个办法
在车前架设镜头，把画面发给警方
警察会明白一切
接电话
-我在  -你觉得你很
-聪明是不是…  -不，闭嘴
我们有你想要的，我要见你
在哪里？
在我上班的地方
给你两小时到那
晚安，混蛋
我老婆在哪？
我的密钥呢？
我老婆在哪儿？
不，不！不！
琳恩！
布兰特？
我要确定这是真的密钥
你
跟着他！
先放了他老婆
天啊，你终于来了
我爱你
怎么样
稍等
我们该走了
杀了他们！
布兰特！小心！
不！不！
-抓住她！  -不！啊！
-你还好吗？  -我没事
靠，他们抓走了那女孩
-我要去救她  -快去
你和警察呆在一起
你慢点！
你受伤了吗？
靠
他有枪
快来救我
听见了没
-你能看见这个平板吗  -嘘！
别说话
布兰特，我把位置发给你
别挡路！
布兰特，你在哪！
-你真他妈是混蛋！  -你闭嘴！
来吧，我们来玩吧
啊！
我靠！
你在干什么？在录影？
拿来！快给我！
妈的！
我靠！
靠
这是唯一一条撤退的路
我知道了
-把枪给我！  -你干什么，老实点！
你死定了？
布兰特，快，快点！
-滚下车！  -什么？
滚下车！
没事吧？
你还好吗？
你被捕了
谢谢
全部后退！
呜！
-我欠你一个人情  是吧？  -你欠我一辆新车
别担心，它只是需要一个修理工
-什么声音？  -不知道
不是我的手机
-喂  -不用谢我
我帮你做到你做不到的事
我看到了你的表现
请原谅我
不能亲自到场
我有点不方便…
你一定想知道他们是谁…
他们都是你狂热的崇拜者
我一直认为你可以在自己的领域独领风骚…
只要你相信自己
你看，你做到了
请允许我对你的妻子致以最诚挚的祝福
我很喜欢她为你准备的圣诞节礼物
多点时间陪陪自己的家人
我没有什么亲人
唯一能安慰我的就是我有很多钱
而现在我看到了你，非常感谢
我们以后还会有交集的
所以，现在还是先说一句
再见
我向你保证…
以后会更加有意思的
字
字幕
字幕制
字幕制作
字幕制作 ★
字幕制作 ★ 至
字幕制作 ★ 至宏
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上人